http://www.toffs.com/privacy-policy

My Bag
(0) item(s)
- £0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Checkout
(0) item(s)
- £0.00
My Bag
(0) item(s)
- £0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Clear Search
(open)PREMIER LEAGUEArsenalBrighton & Hove AlbionBurnleyCardiff CityChelseaCrystal PalaceEvertonFulhamHuddersfield TownLeeds UnitedLeicester CityLiverpoolManchester CityManchester UnitedNewcastle UnitedSouthamptonTottenham HotspurThames IronworksWest Bromwich AlbionWolves(open)CHAMPIONSHIPAston VillaBirmingham CityBlackburn RoversBournemouthBrentfordBristol CityCoventry CityDerby CountyIpswich TownMiddlesbroughMillwallNottingham ForestPreston North EndQueen's Park RangersReadingRotherham UnitedSheffield UnitedSheffield
WednesdayStoke CitySwansea CityWatfordWycombe Wanderers(open)LEAGUE ONEAccrington StanleyBarnsleyBlackpoolBradford CityBristol RoversCharlton AthleticCrewe AlexandraDoncaster RoversGillinghamHull CityLuton TownPeterborough UnitedPlymouth ArgylePortsmouthRochdaleShrewsbury TownScunthorpe UnitedSunderlandSwindon TownWalsallWimbledonWigan Athletic(open)LEAGUE TWOBolton WanderersBuryCambridge UnitedCarlisle UnitedColchester UnitedExeter CityGrimsby TownLincoln CityMansfield TownNewport CountyNorthampton TownNotts CountyOldham AthleticPort ValeSouthend UnitedTranmere Rovers(open)NON LEAGUEAldershotBarnetBath CityBlyth SpartansBradford Park AvenueChesterfieldDarlingtonDulwich HamletGatesheadHalifax TownHartlepool UnitedHereford UnitedLeyton OrientMacclesfield TownMaidstone UnitedNewton HeathNorth ShieldsRoyal EngineersSouthportStockport CountyTorquay UnitedWest AucklandWrexhamYork City(open)MOVIE & FICTIONALShadwell TownEscape to VictoryBarnestoneworth United(open)NASLAtlanta ChiefsEdmonton DrillersCalifornia SurfChicago StingColorado CaribousDetroit CougarsLos Angeles AztecsLos Angeles TorosMemphis RoguesMinnesota KicksMontreal ManicNew York CosmosNew York GeneralsPhiladelphia FuryRochester LancersSeattle SoundersSoccer Bowl Tampa Bay RowdiesTeam AmericaToronto BlizzardToronto FalconsVancouver WhitecapsWashinton Diplomats(open)NORTHERN IRISHBangorArdsColeraineGlentoranCrusadersLinfield(open)INTERNATIONALAlgeriaArgentinaAustraliaBelgiumBrazilBulgariaCameroonCanadaChileColombiaChinaCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCyprusCzechoslovakiaDenmarkEast Germany (DDR)EcuadorEnglandFinlandFranceGermanyGreat BritainGhanaGreeceHollandHungaryIranIcelandIsraelItalyIvory CoastJapanMaltaMexicoNew ZealandNigeriaNorthern IrelandNorth KoreaNorwayParaguayPeruPolandPortugalRepublic of IrelandRomaniaScotlandSouth AfricaSouth KoreaSoviet Union (CCCP)SpainSwedenSwitzerlandTurkeyUruguayUSAVenezuelaWalesWest GermanyYugoslaviaZaire(open)SCOTTISHAberdeenAirdrieoniansAlbion RoversAyr UnitedBerwick RangersCelticClydeDundeeDundee UnitedDunfermlineFalkirkGreenock MortonHamilton AcademicalHeart of MidlothianHibernianKilmarnockMontroseMotherwellPartick ThistleQueen of the SouthQueen's ParkRaith RoversRangersSt MirrenSt JohnstoneThird Lanark(open)IRISHSligo RoversBohemianWaterford UnitedShelbourneDerry CityShamrock Rovers(open)EUROPEANAtletico MadridAC MilanAcademica de CoimbraAEK AthensAGF AarhusAjaxAlessandriaMonacoAnderlechtAmbrosianaAtalantaAvellinoAvenir BeggenBarcelonaReal MadridBastiaBolognaBordeauxBruggeCagliariDinamo ZagrebDukla PragueDynamo KievDynamo MoscowFiorentinaGenoaGrasshoppersHajduk SpiltInternazionale (Inter Milan)JuventusLazioLensLille OSCLyonMalmoMetzNantesNapoli NiceOlympiacosPadovaPalermoPanathinaikosParisPartizan BelgradeRapid BucurestiReal BetisRed Star BelgradeRed Star ParisReimsRoyal AntwerpSaint-EtienneSampdoriaSliema WanderersSporting LisbonTorinoTriestinaValenciaValerengaVeneziaVeronaVicenzaViking StavangerYoung Boys(open)CENTRAL & SOUTH AMERICANBanguBoca JuniorsBotafogoChivas GuadalajaraCobresalColo-ColoCorinthiansEstudiantesFlamengoFluminenseGremioIndependienteInternacionalLeones
NegrosMillonariosPalmeirasPumasRiver PlateSantosSao PauloVasco da Gama(open)REST OF THE WORLDKaizer Chiefs(open)RUGBYArgentinaAustraliaBritish & Irish LionsCanadaEnglandFijiFranceIrelandItalyJapanNew ZealandScotlandSouth AfricaUSAWales(open)CASUALWEARHOODIESPOLOSSHORTSSWEATSHIRTSTRACK TOPST-SHIRTS
TOFFS RETRO(open)FOOTBALL GIFTSDVD(open)BOOKSFootball BooksNewspaper BooksGIFT VOUCHERSHATS & CAPSSCARVESSIGNED PRODUCTS(open)KIDS(open)FOOTBALL(open)PREMIER LEAGUEArsenalBournemouthBurnleyCardiff CityChelseaWatfordCardiffCrystal PalaceEvertonHuddersfield TownLeicester CityLiverpoolManchester CityManchester UnitedNewcastle UnitedSouthamptonThames IronworksTottenham HotspurWolves(open)CHAMPIONSHIPAston VillaBirmingham CityBolton WanderersBrentfordFulhamIpswich TownMiddlesbroughMillwallNottingham ForestPreston North EndQueen's Park RangersSheffield UnitedSheffield WednesdayStoke CitySwansea CityWest Bromwich Albion(open)LEAGUE ONEBarnsleyBlackpoolBristol RoversBradford CityShrewsbury UnitedPortsmouthRochdaleScunthorpe UnitedShrewsbury TownSunderland(open)LEAGUE TWOBuryCarlisle UnitedCrewe AlexandraLuton TownExeter CityOldham AthleticSwindon Town(open)EUROPEANAjaxAtletico MadridBarcelonaBastiaBilbaoAC MilanBordeauxDukla PragueDinamo ZagrebDynamo MoscowHajduk SpiltInternazionale (Inter Milan)JuventusOlympiacosPanathinaikosRed Star BelgradeRomaRoyal AntwerpSporting LisbonValenciaVicenzaParis(open)INTERNATIONALAlgeriaArgentinaAustria BelgiumBrazilCanadaCzechoslovakiaDenmarkEast Germany (DDR)Republic of IrelandEnglandFranceGermanyHollandIsrealItalyJapanMaltaMexicoNorthern IrelandNew ZealandPolandScotlandSpainSwitzerlandUruguaySoviet Union (CCCP)USAWalesWest GermanyYugoslaviaPortugalNorwayIsrealIcelandColombiaSweden(open)NASLAtlanta ChiefsCalifornia SurfNew York CosmosLos Angeles Aztecs(open)CENTRAL & SOUTH AMERICANColo-ColoCorinthiansInternacionalRiver PlateSantos(open)NON LEAGUEEngineers AFCHartlepool UnitedLeyton OrientMacclesfield TownWrexhamYork City(open)SCOTTISHAberdeenCelticClydeDundeeDundee UnitedFalkirkHibernianMontroseQueen of the SouthRaith RoversThird Lanark(open)IRISHBohemianShelbourneWaterford UnitedBohemians(open)NORTHERN IRISHBangorLinfield(open)REST OF THE WORLDKaiser Chiefs(open)RUGBYBritish & Irish LionsArgentinaAustraliaCanadaEnglandFranceItalyNew ZealandScotlandUSAWalesT-SHIRTSHOODIES
BESTSELLERS
TOFFS Ltd. 2016
Home
Privacy Policy
Other Sections
Help & Information
Contact Us
Delivery & Returns
Privacy Policy
The Old Fashioned Football Shirt Co. Limited, trading as TOFFS are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and secondly to provide you with the best service possible. We will only email you in the future if you have previously given us your consent. We will also give you the opportunity to unsubscribe from any future marketing emails.
The type of information we will collect about you when you place an order or register on our web site includes:
Name & Address
Phone Number
Email Address
Sagepay or Paypal process your card details on their secure site to take payment for all orders placed at www.toffs.com.
The above information is stored on our internal systems and our website simply verifies you as a customer of TOFFS. We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. We endeavour to ensure that the information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by visiting your account at www.toffs.com or by emailing us at enquiries@toffs.com. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly. The personal information that we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. We will never share or sell your information to a third party. We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site (see the section on ‘Cookies’ and ‘Analytic Tools’).
Use of personal information
We use the information you provide for the following purposes:
To send updates regarding the status of your enquiry or order
To send newsletters and details of offers and promotions in which we believe you will be interested
To improve the design and content of the toffs.com website.
To perform other general marketing and promotional activities focused on our products and services
When you place an order we need to know your name, email address, delivery address, credit or debit card details. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of the status of your request. We also ask for your telephone number which enables us to contact you urgently if there is a problem with your order.
Your ConsentBy submitting information to TOFFS you consent to the collection and use of this information by TOFFS and its Service Provider (if any). If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Your Email Address
Your e-mail address will be used to communicate with you about your order and products purchased.  Your e-mail address will be used for our marketing purposes unless you unsubscribe. If you do not wish to receive information about our products or services you can unsubscribe by clicking the unsubscribe link, which exists at the bottom of all marketing emails sent by TOFFS.
Data SecurityWe have designed our site to protect the information we collect online from unauthorised access. We safeguard your private information by implementing the appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedure necessary to protect your privacy. To further protect your security, we also take the reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to your personal profile or making data changes. We are committed to protecting your privacy and have security measures in place to prevent unauthorised access to and disclosure of your personal information.
Improving Our ServiceTOFFS do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. To better tailor our services to our customers' needs, we use non-identifying and aggregate information to help us make decisions on how to improve TOFFS. We also do not use or share the personally identifiable information submitted to us by any other means without providing our customers the choice to opt-out or otherwise bar such unrelated uses.
Cookies
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's (or alternative web browsing device’s) hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognise your browser and to provide shopping features such as suggested products, as well as the storage of items in your Shopping Basket between visits. The Help menu in most common browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of TOFFS essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on.
Analytic Tools
Google Analytics is a system used by many websites to record information about visits to their website. Google set six different cookies with expiry dates ranging from 30 minutes to 2 years. These cookies are used mainly to differentiate between first time visitors to a website and repeat visitors. They also allow us to ensure our website performs as well as possible for our users. The cookies are able to collect an anonymous customer number when a user is logged into the website, allowing our backend systems to ensure accuracy of Google Analytics data and help us ensure your website experience remains relevant across devices. They do not contain any personally identifiable information. You can find out more about how Google use cookies at http://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/ (English only)
Social Media Plug-ins
Social Media Plug-ins for Facebook and Twitter obtain data for tracking purposes.
International Privacy
The above privacy statement may not be applicable in all countries of TOFFS visitors or registered community users, as security policies may vary according to the individual Internet laws in each host country.
Disclosures
We will not pass your information to any third parties. You can also email us to stop receiving any information about us and our services. If you have any queries about our Privacy Statement you should contact us by e-mail enquiries@toffs.com
CONTACT
Unit 11C, Station Approach, Earlsway, Gateshead, Team Valley, NE11 0ZF
Pay securely with...
eCommerce By CShop
Cookie Terms
This site uses cookies to give you the best shopping experience on our site. By continuing to use this site, you agree to accept these cookies.
Click here to view our cookie information.
Top
